Mahmoud ElHassan Mahmoud

51 Ibn Rahmon St, Hadra, Alexandria

📱 +201005152604 | 💌 mahmoudelhassan9@gmail.com | 🖸 portfolio-mahmoudelhassan.vercel.app | 🛅 www.linkedin.com/in/mahmoud-elhassan-94r

Personal Profile

An ITI Institute graduate student enrolled in the track full-stack web development .Net and Angular. Dedicated to software engineering, having two or more years of expertise, and specializing in full-stack web development, and algorithms. Searching mainly for Back-end, Front-end, and Database.

Education

M.K.S Language School,

Smouha, Alexandria, Egypt

High School

May 2013

Faculty of Tourism and Hotels at Alexandria University

Alexandria, Egypt June 2013 - June 2017

Bachelor at Hotels Management Department

Information Technology Institute (ITI)

Alexandria , Egypt

Diploma at track Full Stack web development .Net and Angular

August 2022 - November 2022

Work Experience

Hilton Green Plaza

Alexandria, Egypt

Front office Agent July 2017 - November 2019

Americana Group KFC

Rahrain

Assistant Restaurant Manager

January 2020 - October 2021

Upwork, Kahmsat, Mostaqel

Online
November 2022 - Till Now

Freelancer

Astro Website Remotely

.Net Developer March 2023 - Till Now

Click To visit the WebSite

Projects

Back-End

Astro pvt Project

- Database structure by SQL Server with EF core.
- REST APIs by ASP.Net core based on Repositories Pattern based on client request design like Soft Delete and static Data Structure.
- Technical Used: SQL Server, ASP.Net core, and C Sharp.
- Click To see the Code

E-Commerce Back-End

Freelancing Project

- Database structure by SQL Server with EF core.
- REST APIs by ASP.Net core based on Repositories Pattern.
- Technical Used: SQL Server, ASP.Net core, and C Sharp.
- Click To see the Code

AirBNB Demo Back-End

ITI Project

- Database structure by SQL Server with EF core.
- REST APIs by ASP.Net core.
- Technical Used: SQL Server, ASP.Net core, and C Sharp.
- Click To see the Code

AUGUST 28, 2023

Desktop Application

ITI Project

- Demo for Sanke and Ladders game with ASP.Net as a Desktop Application.
- Database structure by EF core. and C Sharp.
- Technical Used: ASP.Net core, and C Sharp.
- Click To see the Code

Skills

Programming ASP.Net | ASP.Net core (C, JQuery, Ajax, Jason, etc.), HTML/CSS, JavaScript, SQL Server, Angular JS, and React JS

Miscellaneous Microsoft Office, Firebase, and GitHub.

Soft Skills Time Management, Teamwork, Problem-solving, Documentation, and Engaging Presentation.

Certificate

2022 **Udacity**, Web Development

2022 Mahara-Tech, Database Fundamentals

2022 Mahara-Tech, JavaScript

2022 **Mahara-Tech**, Freelancing

2020 **Baharain**, Yum Courses Online: Food Safety, Delivery, FOH, MOH, BOH, LAS

2016 Alexandria University, COMSYS Program

2015 Alexandria University, Awards HACCP Program

Languages _____

English Professional proficiency **Arabic** Native proficiency